Seino, girl-girl channel, go-go!
Yes, so ice cream is here for this collaboration project.
Please introduce yourself.
Yes, hello everyone who is watching Galgal Channel, I'm Ice Cream.
I'm Louis.
I'm Yuna.
I'm Hinata.
Hello, I'm Yuna.
Today's project is werewolf dance.
I wanted to try it.
We're going to put on earphones and play Rocksteady for the civilian side and THE FINEST, the other coupling, for the werewolf side.
The base of the game is that everyone dances rocksteady to find out who the werewolf is.
I wonder if it's possible to do this.
I'm sure it is.
Someone who has gotten good at it.
I've practiced with werewolves before, haven't I?
Yes, I have.
We've only had werewolves win.
Citizens have won.
Then I'd like to start with the lottery to decide who will be the werewolf.
I'm so excited.
Three this time?
Yes, that's right. We will draw lots to decide who will be the 3 werewolves this time.
So that only you can see them.
Can we spread out a little more?
Wait a minute.
Let's open it up.
Bye-bye.
You all saw it, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Please close your eyes for a moment.
Let's open only for werewolves.
Werewolves, open your eyes.
Are you okay?
Who's there?
You're here. There are wolves here.You're here. There are wolves here.
There are wolves.
Werewolves.
Werewolves are wolves.
Let the werewolf dance music begin!
We in Rock City
We meet you in every moment
In dreams and wished times elistwise
Also we same memories
Oh, no! There's something fishy in here!
What do you think?
Yeah, there was a pretty shady guy.
Yeah, he's been calling me all the time.
What?
No, I doubt it. I doubt it.
Weird.
Why are you suspicious?
No, but Yudan is suspicious, too.
I'm with Sparkles.
I don't know.
I don't know. I don't think anyone listens to Final Street.
What?
Why?
Oh, perfect.
Nobody listens to Final Street.
Well, some people do.
No one sings it.
Elo parie lo terra. Elo parie lo terra.
Yeah.
It's already intertwined with us in the lines
We're all tangled up
I don't suspect anyone.
What? What? What?
Not sirens.
What?What?
What was that?
No, seriously, I don't know.
But you know what?
You're the one with the lines.
Why are you doing this with Yashinchan?
Let's go have a little fun.
Come on.
Hey, you guys are good.
You're all so good.
Are they all in sync?
This is the finalist, and whoever's listening is really good.
You're all so good.
It's getting hard to tell.
That's so weird.
Yeah, he was.
Isn't it the end of the line?
One, two, three, four.
I know who it is.
But it's the end of the line.
There's a lot of shady people out there.
It's the end of the line.
It's over!
What?
I don't know who the chairman is.
I'll get it. One time.
I'll take out the suspicious ones, I guess.
Yes, so, once the dancing is over now, it's the first night, right?
Yes.
Oh!
We will talk for two minutes and process two people who we think are werewolves.
Yes.
Three times. We've got three rounds.
On this first turn, I'd like to decide on one for now.
Right.Yes, that's right.
Three times properly. three people will come if you go one at a time.
No, but there were a lot of suspicious people.
There were.
Let's get a lot of them out.
I'm Rui.
Me?
I don't know, the spark was off, but then it all came together.
That's suspicious.
This?
It was way off.
That part was wrong, wasn't it?
But in the chorus, it's all right.
It's all there.
It's weird.
Suspicious.
In my experience as a girl, people who are suspicious usually do that.
Well, experience speaks louder than words.
How about that?
Sure, there's an excuse.
But I've been watching YouTube for a while now,
I've seen the YouTube videos, and I've heard a lot of advice from people,
I got advice from everyone, both on the civilian side and the werewolf side,
I did my best.
They didn't say.
I was a werewolf.
Each.
I was not.
I was misled by each werewolf's moves.
Suspicious.
Too suspicious.
I, I don't want to be a werewolf. I said I'm not good at it.
I hate it.
I'm in no hurry,I'm not even in a hurry,
The sorry feeling is very suspicious.
If I were a citizen, I would be a little more responsive.
I'd say, "I'm a citizen of Louisville on my own,
I'm a citizen of Louis.
He's calm.
No, I've already admitted it.
I'm going to stick my teeth out and do this.
How do you see this?
I don't see it as a game of rock-paper-scissors.
As a suspect.
Expulsion may be for each.
What else?
I was suspicious of Louie, too,
The scurrying group,
Kira Minami and Yuna.
I can see that. Yuna, too.
Sure, sure.
But that's because I wanted to see it.
Because I wanted to see werewolves,
It's all pretty much the same.
I didn't know because it was pretty disjointed.
I thought they were scurrying around in Minamikira.
But you know how sometimes Yuna gets lost in the shadows?
Everyone is.
When they can't coordinate with each other, they just kind of go like this.
Finally, I saw her.
What?
I can't see this.
Wait, wait.
Kira and Kira Minami.
That's what I'd do if I killed Yuna.
Why was Kira looking around to see what was going on?
Kira was with you, right?
We were together a lot.We were together quite a bit.
Who I think is Louie.
Once.
Then, those who think it's Toa.
Those who think it's Kira.
Not yet. We'll talk.
Did the coordination work?
Those who think Momotaro.
Who thinks it's Minami?
One person.
One.
But I'm in first place.
Let's go with "South" then.
Are you guys giving him a chain? Yes.
Just the two of you?
If you kill Yuna, I'll do it.
I'll tell you what.
I don't know. I don't know anyone anymore.
The ones who think it's Kira.
Those who think it's Yuna.
Those who think it's Rioka.
I don't know, everyone.
What are you going to do when ice cream is announced in three minutes?
I think it's probably true because he doesn't talk much in these situations.
It seems easy to understand.
This is Jimin from Louie.
Say, "Are you a werewolf or a jiminy?
Get to the front of the line in front of the camera.
Okay?
I'm a werewolf.
Of course you are.
Too soon.
Then I'm Yuna.
I am not a werewolf.
I'm stopped at werewolf.
I'd like you to stop at werewolf.I'd like you to stop with the werewolves.
You didn't know about the weapons.
In werewolves.
Can I tell you why I think it's Toa?
You said it.
Yuna was suspicious of Toa and looked at him like this.
And you know what, before 1, 2, 3.
Yuna's position was next to me.
To watch.
It was simple.
By mistake.
I was doing this with the radio signal.
If I could hear the sound, I wouldn't have done it.
This was a good place.
I did it twice.
Like, "It's 1, 2, 3.
I said, "Not here.
He looked at me, so I did it.
I'm the only one who covered Rui right now.
That's for sure.
While I was raising my hands.
And you know what they're like.
They've been bonding lately.
That's right. It's related.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I don't know.
I think we're just posturing there.
Didn't we talk about glitter?
What's going on?
Did you see something?
Did you see something? I did.
Then what happened?
Did you see something? My werewolf thing.
Did you see it?
I don't know.I don't know.
This?
I want to hear it so bad.
It's a lie.
What do you mean?
I can't stop looking at myself like I'm a werewolf.
We don't have time for this. I don't have time.
Next, who's suspicious?
And Yuna?
Minami.
Why? Why?
It's a little suspicious.
It's a little weird.
So, who thinks it's me?
Who thinks it's Toa?
Too soon.
Then who do you think is Kira?
Who thinks it's Sam?
Then let's vote for Toa.
Because Toa is still alive.
Minami.
Why?
But, I mean, isn't he a werewolf?
I see. Yes, he is.
Well, we'll have another turn.
There's always a next turn.
You'll have to sacrifice once.
What? That's funny. Oh, man.
Which one do you want to go first?
What are you doing?
I don't know. I'm a little suspicious.
This vote. I don't know.
I'll just say it then.
I'm a werewolf.
That's suspicious.
You know what?It's that thing already.
That's for sure.
See? It's really different.
Here we go.
I'm not a werewolf.
You were with me.
I'm serious.
I was giving it to Minami.
It was a little psychological before.
What's wrong?
You said you were a werewolf.
To whom?
Miki.
And he nodded his head and said no.
No. No.
I see.
You came here without knowing my body, right?
Huh?
It's a face.
What? No, no, no.
Huh?
That's weird.
He's talking a lot,
He's writing.
He's gonna write.
No, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Right here, right here.
Is that right? No? Say that,
Like this often.
No, I don't.
What? I saw it. I saw it.
It's really different.
You can decide.
What? What? I can decide?
Who's the most suspicious?Who is the most suspicious?
I guess it's me and Miki right now.
Oh, no. Oh, my God. You're saying that?
Try smiling.
It's really different.
My mouth is getting sandy.
No, it's not.
Let's get out of here.
No luck.
But I'm wondering if it's Yuzu or Kirara's.
Miki is the most suspicious.
It's either Yuzu or Kirara.
Maybe it's Kira.
It's not Kira.
Okay, let's vote now.
Who do you think is Kira?
What? You don't mind, do you?
Hmm?
Kira, be confident.
From Miki?
From Miki.
Melo!
Here we go.
I'm a werewolf.
I'm not a werewolf.
You believed me so much.
Yoka-chan.
Then, let's hope.
I am not a werewolf.
I'm not a werewolf.
Yay.
Who? Who?
Oh, man.
You're making me so sad that I have to run away.
Why did you do that?
I made a huge mistake.I missed it by a long shot.
You mean it was raining a lot?
Yes.
I had to survive so I could win.
I was scared shitless, but I was good.
Well, thank you, werewolf. Victory.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
On the flip side, did anyone see Claire's weird scene while we were dancing?
I didn't see anyone because I was bumping into her.
You didn't show any suspicious scenes?
Claire was a little bit in tune with everyone.
Everyone has a weird scene.
As Yoka said, I was the one who did it at KB3.
1, 2, 3.
I was too taken by Yoka's position to do it in a groove.
Think I'm doing it.
Cream.
Thank you for watching.
If you found this video interesting, please give it a high rating, comment, and subscribe to our channel.
We will do our best to collaborate with ice cream again, so please continue to enjoy our Galgal channel.
Thank you very much.
Please listen to Rock Steady.
This time we are wearing D Hollick's costumes.
Next time, I will be wearing D Hollick's costume.